BGM
Please
The theme should be rock with a U-type rock feel.
The theme should be rock with a punk-ish rock feel to it.
The theme image should be red check with black rider's jacket.
A little bit see-through.
BGM
Something like that
Red or black?
BGM
The image of U type
It's like that.
Okay.
BGM
Leave the rest to SOPPY
But I think the skirt is better.
BGM
I don't know, it's just an image.
I wonder what it would be like to perform live.
BGM
I guess so.
I see.
BGM
BGM.
BGM BGM
BGM
BGMBGM
BGMBNG
BGMB
BGM
Nice
And pad shield at the time of shooting
Certainly
You have a good arm where you can get in.
Yeah, I guess I am.
And then we shoot.
Shooting.
It's not so much that I want to take a nice shot inside.
I think it's better to shoot outside.
Like in a garage.
I think it's better to find a place
I'd like to find a place with a lot of backs.
I'll try to find a place with a lot of backs.
Black and white is cool, too.
Yeah.
I like the makeup.
It's better to have a lot of make-up.
I want to be spicy. I'd like to be a little gorier.
I was thinking...
What do you think?
The atmosphere of the scene
Like this
It's so crisp.
What will happen?
As long as it's cool.
I don't care what it looks like.
Whatever's cool.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah. - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's more like nighttime.
Yeah.
It's not like daytime is rough.
Yeah, it's...
It's nighttime.
Night.
Maybe not so much sun.
Image.
Yeah. - Yeah.
So...
Yes, sir.
I'll think about it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I saw a little bit of everyone.
They're all cute.
Oh, my God.
Who's this?
That's me.
I see...
Is it because of that performance?
They're all kind of...
They're cute.
I don't know if it's cute.
Is it nice?
Well, there's a lot of people who'd like to see it.
Yeah. Right.
Regular idol costumes.
Yup.
Cute.
Cure.
Wow.
Looks like a cure.
So cute!
Mirage
Amazing!
Mirage!
Cute.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
You want to see it, right?
Yeah. - Yeah.
That feels good.
Here.
Her feet are out in front of her.
Right?
Ha-ha-ha.
Here you go.
If this is what you want to say...
It's not me.
Can you see it?
If you cut it, you can see it.
If you cut it off...
It's Chinese.
You don't have this, do you?
Yes, yes, yes. oh, yes!
this
Looks strong
Definitely looks strong
That villain
This resident
This is his neck.
Spikes.
Maybe he's going for a tattoo.
He's cute.
Cute.
Iwa-chan's
What kind of tattoos do you guys have?
Let's get a tattoo
We all forget
Gangster
Gangs.
I don't like it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's easy to cut corners.
Yes, it is.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's easy to cut corners.
I see it. I see it.
I see it again.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
That's it.
It looks great with a wide lens.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure. Yes, sir.
You want to take another black one upstairs?
You want to take it?
contractor
Oh, smok took it.
He took it for me.
I don't know.
Shangha
This
It's not good.
He looks...
Only one of us is in trouble.
He's not doing what everyone else is doing.
Sit down and stretch out your legs.
Stretch out your legs.
Stretch your legs out.
Okay. - Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
How do you feel now?
I'm happy.
It's full of my favorite things.
The hair and makeup, of course.
And the costumes.
I love everything about it.
I've gathered all of my favorite things.
You all decorated it, so I'm very happy.
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much.
It's a precious opportunity.
I think they all look pretty cute.
I have the impression that there are a lot of pretty people.
I have the impression that they are all very pretty.
the most.
I was able to go to the rock I was able to go to the rock.
I think that was a good thing.
Look at the pictures.
I was thinking that it's different when I take pictures
It was important for me
It was important for me to fill it with what I like.
I am satisfied.
Thank you very much.
I'm not sure what kind of live show I want to do.
Actually, I'm still a little bit confused about what kind of show it should be.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not.
I'd like to play a lot of Gangnam Pirates' rock songs.
I'm not sure if I want to rearrange them to make them more
I'd like to rearrange the songs
or make a medley of songs so that we can have a lot of songs
I thought it would be good to try a new challenge
I think it would be good to try something new
I'm still a little unsure about that.
But I'd like to sing all of them live.
I'd like to sing all the parts live.
In terms of live performance
I think we will be able to deliver something
I'm sure we'll be able to deliver something that we haven't had in Gangparade so far.
I hope you can look forward to it.
Please vote for us!
Thank you for your attention and your vote!
Whee!
I really can't believe it!
Sure, sure, sure.
Forced
Forced.g